elliott.org 2002-10-16

# ELLIOTT.ORG: Privacy Policy

Elliott.org respects your right to the privacy of the personal information you provide us. To that end, unless you designate otherwise or we state otherwise in this policy or at the time information is collected, any personal information you provide to elliott.org will be known only to two parties: you and elliott.org. The following policy is intended to explain how your personal information will be treated as you make use of this site. Personal information includes your name, street and e-mail addresses, click-through activity and any other personal information you may provide here. This policy may change from time to time, so please check back periodically. 

**Traffic data**

Each time a visitor comes to elliott.org, our servers - like most on the Web - collect some basic technical information, including, for example, the visitor's domain name, referral data and browser and platform type. 

We also count, track and aggregate the visitor's activity into our analysis of general traffic flows at our sites. To these ends, we may merge information about visitors and visits into group data, which may then be shared on an aggregated basis with our advertisers; but we will not disclose your individual identity or personally identifiable data without your permission. When we do present aggregated information to outside companies, no one will be able to identify you or contact you. 

**E-mails**

Elliott.org asks senders of e-mails to include contact information so we can make an effort to verify their identity should we need to in connection with publication of a letter. We do not retain this information for any other purpose, nor do we sell, trade or otherwise disclose it to third parties. 

**Promotion**

From time to time, elliott.org may sponsor sweepstakes, contests or other events which require the collection, processing and storage of individual contact and demographic information to be used for the event. Elliott.org may also co-sponsor these events along with other companies, in which case the user's individual contact and demographic information is likely to be shared with other participating sponsors, who may use this information as they wish. A registrant's personal contact and demographic information will not be released to any third-party organization other than named sponsors without the user's consent, and elliott.org will request that such named sponsors uphold the privacy of the registrants' information by not distributing or sharing such information with any other businesses or organizations. 

**Surveys**

Elliott.org will from time to time conduct voluntary surveys of visitors to the site to obtain aggregate demographic information about them. Such information may be compiled and shared in the aggregate with advertisers and other third parties, but no personal details will be traceable or associated with specific individuals. 

**Our commitment to children's privacy**

Protecting the privacy of the very young is important to us. For that reason, we do not collect or maintain information at our Web sites from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our Web site is structured to attract anyone under 13. 

**Other disclosure of personal information**

Elliott.org will not otherwise use or disclose your personal information without your consent except (i) as described in this privacy policy, or (ii) as required by law, court order or as requested by other government or law enforcement authority. This policy does not protect information you post to any on-line bulletin board, chat room, newsgroup or other public forum within our Web sites. 

**Other sites**

Elliott.org contains many links to other sites on the Web. We cannot control and are not responsible for the privacy practices or content of such other Web sites. 

**Who can I ask if I have any additional questions?**

If you have any further questions or concerns about elliott.org's privacy policies and use of personal information, please send them to [privacy@elliott.org](mailto:privacy@elliott.org).
